12 o'clock already body restaurant City This is
what I English Listening part this video
you can use speedo the fastest warning
and understand like speak the voice
talk Vietnam buddhist out itself or fat
and forward instead use and today I'm
gonna talk about past British National
income tax because the more you Some
high the station and Well Well talk
about that affect takes the fastest
wintour paratype thanks Which is the
software in other countries people are
you the world metrowest undergrad I Knew
You Were we usually ships of many cities
around the world have with such in
cities like Paris wondered Tokyo picture
of Western Union Ag d
a Software and is this a very organized
and fish However many big cities in you
were gonna have good Where most people
in us trichan number here don't need it take
to Somewhere in my hometown The surgery
We don't have where i live in the
Somewhere ikanji spica message You can
go anywhere in the city with our
thoughts in something is the Subway
Station support area and Monsters
University careful you take that away Ok
another for punch in State in perth big
cities have passed system State of
polish in  something this passage all
nights Princess in addition this passage
is  untrusted reynolds
Em in Mexico most stores your own and
uncomfortable with all of these Days
because masteri dashed Line will reap
and Drive Fast and they often have added
most typical White teeth in pairs at
some time that I managed Kaspersky pure
our money the person That is good Ok Now
Let's talk about taxis and tubing in the
as many people all taxes Nowadays many
people you could i love you are Used
over time you new prince Triple
protection and you'll save file Which is
still see you There could i speak and
utensils and Wide  taxi or use the
expense in cities Print facility
people can use it How are you do
You're print lucid Ok not Common type
Urban Station is right about this great
way to move and the city [ __ ] is
Riding boots were tall is the kosman is
its single since it in some cities
strivers gottfried So I think you
supplied by industry and other cities as
your patience and diseases in things or
just like the five in the [ __ ] one more
paper can't Touch this Watch Vision My
pivot table transportation tickets There
is free and fast file word picture of
the outside  If I Ever tried out more
tourists especially their lives for me
and tell me what  TP
two candidates your paper and forever just
like that occurs in for a person
Instagram for more English language of
decision e